[{
    "question":"In which lane do you want to play ?",
    "answer":["top","jungler","mid","adc","support"],
    "nb_answer":"multiple",
    "id":0
},
{
    "question":"Do you want to be a melee or a range ?",
    "answer":["melee","range"],
    "nb_answer":"single",
    "id":1
},
{
    "question":"Do you want to deal magic or physical damage ?",
    "answer":["magic","physical"],
    "nb_answer":"multiple",
    "id":2
},
{
    "question":"What is the maximum difficulty ?",
    "answer":["easy","moderate","hard"],
    "nb_answer":"single",
    "id":3
},
{
    "question":"Which role do you like best?",
    "answer":["assassin","fighter","mage","marksmen","enchanters","tank"],
    "nb_answer":"multiple",
    "id":4
},
{
    "question":"Are you more confident with abilities or attacks ?",
    "answer":["abilities","attacks"],
    "nb_answer":"multiple",
    "id":5
},
{
    "question":"What is the minimal acceptable mobility?",
    "answer":["not very mobile","mobile","very mobile"],
    "nb_answer":"single",
    "id":6
},
{
    "question":"Does your champion require a dash?",
    "answer":["yes","no"],
    "nb_answer":"single",
    "id":7
},
{
    "question":"Do you prefer early or late game ?",
    "answer":["early","hybrid","late"],
    "nb_answer":"single",
    "id":8
},
{
    "question":"Would you rather deals AOE or single target damage ?",
    "answer":["aoe","hybrid","single"],
    "nb_answer":"single",
    "id":9
}]